{
    "hero_title": "Do you have the mentality of an Olympian?",
    "hero_subtitle": "Take our 60 second quiz and see if you have what's needed to win gold, regardless of your sporting ability.",
    "start_quiz": "Take quiz",
    "olympic_medal_icon_alt_text": "Olympic medal icon",
    "": "",
    "question_13_number": "13/13",
    "question_13_question": "How old are you?",
    "question_13_highest": "11-16",
    "question_13_high": "17-35",
    "question_13_mid": "36-65",
    "question_13_low": "66 and over",
    "question_1_number": "1/13",
    "question_1_result_noun": "conscientiousness",
    "question_1_result_noun_strength": "",
    "question_1_result_noun_weakness": "",
    "question_1_question": "Are you slapdash or spot on?",
    "question_1_highest": "I'm spot on",
    "question_1_high": "I'm spot on, mostly",
    "question_1_mid": "I'm somewhere in the middle",
    "question_1_low": "I'm a little slapdash",
    "question_1_lowest": "I'm very slapdash",
    "question_1_feedback": "If you're thorough, vigilant and pay close attention to detail you're likely to be successful across many areas of life, not just sport. It's also unlikely to change during your lifetime, so scoring well here makes a big difference. If you didn't, it's time to knuckle down.",
    "question_1_score_highest": "5",
    "question_1_score_high": "4",
    "question_1_score_med": "3",
    "question_1_score_low": "2",
    "question_1_score_lowest": "1",
    "question_2_number": "2/13",
    "question_2_result_noun": "perfectionism",
    "question_2_result_noun_strength": "",
    "question_2_result_noun_weakness": "",
    "question_2_question": "110% effort or easy roller?",
    "question_2_highest": "Always maximum effort",
    "question_2_high": "Maximum effort sometimes",
    "question_2_mid": "I'm somewhere in the middle",
    "question_2_low": "I'm tempted by the easy option",
    "question_2_lowest": "Easy roller every time",
    "question_2_feedback": "Perfectionists tend to strive for greatness but never get there, no matter how successful they become. So while this trait can be useful for a top athlete, being too tough on yourself may hold you back so keep those goals realistic.",
    "question_2_score_highest": "5",
    "question_2_score_high": "4",
    "question_2_score_med": "3",
    "question_2_score_low": "2",
    "question_2_score_lowest": "1",
    "question_3_number": "3/13",
    "question_3_result_noun": "mental toughness",
    "question_3_result_noun_strength": "",
    "question_3_result_noun_weakness": "",
    "question_3_question": "Fly or flop when the going gets hot?",
    "question_3_highest": "Super fly",
    "question_3_high": "Fly",
    "question_3_mid": "I'm somewhere in the middle",
    "question_3_low": "Flop",
    "question_3_lowest": "Total flop",
    "question_3_feedback": "You're on the blocks at the 100m final, an audience of millions is watching your every step, can you cope? Regardless of circumstance, the elite athletes are able to cope when the pressure is on.",
    "question_3_score_highest": "5",
    "question_3_score_high": "4",
    "question_3_score_med": "3",
    "question_3_score_low": "2",
    "question_3_score_lowest": "1",
    "question_4_number": "4/13",
    "question_4_result_noun": "ego",
    "question_4_result_noun_strength": "",
    "question_4_result_noun_weakness": "",
    "question_4_question": "Are you a rock star or a wallflower?",
    "question_4_highest": "Rock super star!",
    "question_4_high": "Rock star",
    "question_4_mid": "I'm somewhere in the middle",
    "question_4_low": "I'm a bit of a wallflower",
    "question_4_lowest": "Total wallflower",
    "question_4_feedback": "Whether you relish the limelight or shy away from it, having a big ego can be helpful for athletes, particularly in individual sports. Being the centre of attention and handling criticism well will stand you in good stead. But remember, no one likes a show off!",
    "question_4_score_highest": "5",
    "question_4_score_high": "4",
    "question_4_score_med": "3",
    "question_4_score_low": "2",
    "question_4_score_lowest": "1",
    "question_5_number": "5/13",
    "question_5_result_noun": "competitiveness",
    "question_5_result_noun_strength": "",
    "question_5_result_noun_weakness": "",
    "question_5_question": "Take on the competition or check out of the rat race?",
    "question_5_highest": "I love to compete",
    "question_5_high": "I like to compete",
    "question_5_mid": "I'm somewhere in the middle",
    "question_5_low": "I only enter the rat race if I have to",
    "question_5_lowest": "No rat race for me!",
    "question_5_feedback": "There can only be one winner, right? Having a competitive streak is very important so beating the rivals should be your focus.",
    "question_5_score_highest": "5",
    "question_5_score_high": "4",
    "question_5_score_med": "3",
    "question_5_score_low": "2",
    "question_5_score_lowest": "1",
    "question_6_number": "6/13",
    "question_6_result_noun": "proactive approach",
    "question_6_result_noun_strength": "",
    "question_6_result_noun_weakness": "",
    "question_6_question": "Do you start the party or wait for the invite?",
    "question_6_highest": "I always get it started! Why wait?",
    "question_6_high": "I like to try",
    "question_6_mid": "Sometimes, it depends..",
    "question_6_low": "I usually wait for the invite",
    "question_6_lowest": "I never get the party started",
    "question_6_feedback": "Good things don't always come to those who wait. Seize the day and make it yours if you want to succeed.",
    "question_6_score_highest": "5",
    "question_6_score_high": "4",
    "question_6_score_med": "3",
    "question_6_score_low": "2",
    "question_6_score_lowest": "1",
    "question_7_number": "7/13",
    "question_7_result_noun": "motivation",
    "question_7_result_noun_strength": "",
    "question_7_result_noun_weakness": "",
    "question_7_question": "Do you do things for the love of the game or material gain?",
    "question_7_highest": "For the love of the game",
    "question_7_high": "I'd say like, rather than love",
    "question_7_mid": "I'm somewhere in the middle",
    "question_7_low": "Material gain is my main motivation",
    "question_7_lowest": "Material gain is my only motivation",
    "question_7_feedback": "How motivated are you? Often found on job adverts, it's there for a reason - being motivated, particularly when people aren't watching is one of the key factors in being successful.",
    "question_7_score_highest": "5",
    "question_7_score_high": "4",
    "question_7_score_med": "3",
    "question_7_score_low": "2",
    "question_7_score_lowest": "1",
    "question_8_number": "8/13",
    "question_8_result_noun": "task orientation",
    "question_8_result_noun_strength": "",
    "question_8_result_noun_weakness": "",
    "question_8_question": "Push back or push on?",
    "question_8_highest": "I face tasks head on",
    "question_8_high": "I'll do it, but only if it benefits me",
    "question_8_mid": "I'd rather not",
    "question_8_low": "I'm happy in my comfort zone",
    "question_8_lowest": "Do I have to do it?",
    "question_8_feedback": "Caring about improving your personal best is key for high performance in sport. Do you care where you come in comparison with others, or where how compare with yourself?",
    "question_8_score_highest": "5",
    "question_8_score_high": "4",
    "question_8_score_med": "3",
    "question_8_score_low": "2",
    "question_8_score_lowest": "1",
    "question_9_number": "9/13",
    "question_9_result_noun": "self confidence",
    "question_9_result_noun_strength": "",
    "question_9_result_noun_weakness": "",
    "question_9_question": "Back yourself or sack yourself?",
    "question_9_highest": "My self believe is unshakable",
    "question_9_high": "Yes, I'm a confident person",
    "question_9_mid": "I'd back myself, just about",
    "question_9_low": "I'm not very confident",
    "question_9_lowest": "I'm not at all confident",
    "question_9_feedback": "Self-confidence is key to sporting ability – just ask Cristiano Ronaldo… But it swings dramatically depending on the situation so even Cristiano has dips in confidence.",
    "question_9_score_highest": "5",
    "question_9_score_high": "4",
    "question_9_score_med": "3",
    "question_9_score_low": "2",
    "question_9_score_lowest": "1",
    "question_10_number": "10/13",
    "question_10_result_noun": "focus",
    "question_10_result_noun_strength": "",
    "question_10_result_noun_weakness": "",
    "question_10_question": "Focused or forgetful?",
    "question_10_highest": "100% in the zone",
    "question_10_high": "I can multi-task, what's next?",
    "question_10_mid": "I've got this far...",
    "question_10_low": "Daydreamer",
    "question_10_lowest": "What was the question again?",
    "question_10_feedback": "So you're still with us? Did you make it through without getting distracted? The brain can only focus on a limited amount of things at once so focusing on what matters is key to succeeding.",
    "question_10_score_highest": "5",
    "question_10_score_high": "4",
    "question_10_score_med": "3",
    "question_10_score_low": "2",
    "question_10_score_lowest": "1",
    "question_11_number": "11/13",
    "question_11_result_noun": "social support",
    "question_11_result_noun_strength": "",
    "question_11_result_noun_weakness": "",
    "question_11_question": "Go it alone or look for help?",
    "question_11_highest": "I go it alone. I can cope by myself",
    "question_11_high": "I got it alone, most of the time",
    "question_11_mid": "I'm somewhere in the middle",
    "question_11_low": "I look for help some of the time",
    "question_11_lowest": "I always look for help when i need it",
    "question_11_feedback": "Need support? Team-mates, friends, colleagues, Steve at the desk behind you, they all can help boost your performance so seek it out when you need it.",
    "question_11_score_highest": "5",
    "question_11_score_high": "4",
    "question_11_score_med": "3",
    "question_11_score_low": "2",
    "question_11_score_lowest": "1",
    "question_12_number": "12/13",
    "question_12_result_noun": "goal-setting",
    "question_12_result_noun_strength": "",
    "question_12_result_noun_weakness": "",
    "question_12_question": "Target driven or hope for the best?",
    "question_12_highest": "Yes, targets are my only friend",
    "question_12_high": "I'm pretty target driven",
    "question_12_mid": "I'm somewhere in the middle",
    "question_12_low": "Only at New Year",
    "question_12_lowest": "Targets are for other people",
    "question_12_feedback": "Goals – scoring them and setting them are vital to succeeding. Track them, measure them and stick to them. Without them you'll drift through tasks.",
    "question_12_score_highest": "5",
    "question_12_score_high": "4",
    "question_12_score_med": "3",
    "question_12_score_low": "2",
    "question_12_score_lowest": "1",
    "This question behaves differently ...": "",
    "question_14_number": "13/13",
    "question_14_question": "How physically active are you?",
    "question_14_high": "Very",
    "question_14_mid": "Somewhere in the middle",
    "question_14_low": "Not a lot",
    "question_14_score_high": "poss alt text results text",
    "question_14_score_med": "poss alt text results text",
    "question_14_score_low": "poss alt text results text",
    "see_results": "See results",
    "retake_quiz": "Take the quiz again",
    "results_category_1": "Olympian",
    "results_category_2": "Solid athlete",
    "results_category_3": "Fitness fan",
    "results_category_4": "Weekend stroller",
    "results_category_5": "Day dreamer",
    "results_category_1_total": "49",
    "results_category_2_total": "48",
    "results_category_3_total": "36",
    "results_category_4_total": "30",
    "results_category_5_total": "18",
    "results_category_1_text": "Congratulations! You have the mindset needed to challenge at the top level of competitive sport. Good luck in Rio!",
    "results_category_2_text": "You have most of the strengths needed to be a good athlete, but you may struggle to challenge Usain Bolt and co on the medals podium.",
    "results_category_3_text": "You don't have the mentality to compete in Olympic sport, but you would be a great asset to any local sports team. Step it up if you want to make the 2020 Games",
    "results_category_4_text": "It seems that you don't have the mentality of an Olympian, but you could still enjoy sport at a recreational level. Time for a run?",
    "results_category_5_text": "It may come as no surprise that you don't seem to have the mental habits of an Olympian but you can still enjoy sport and exercise as a way of keeping active.",
    "strengths_text": "Your main strengths are",
    "weakness_text": "But you could improve your",
    "activity_1_text": "Find more information on getting involved in sport at",
    "activity_1_url": "http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/get-inspired",
    "activity_1_url_title": "BBC Get Inspired",
    "activity_2_text": "Find more information on getting started with sport and exercise at",
    "activity_2_url": "http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/p03m53p1",
    "activity_2_url_title": "BBC Make your Move",
    "legacy_ie_message": "You should upgrade to a modern browser."
}